<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on @rithy.org</title>
    <link>http://rithy.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on @rithy.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Copyright notice</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 11:12:07 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://rithy.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lesson from Music &amp; Artists</title>
      <link>http://rithy.org/posts/lesson-from-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 11:12:07 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rithy.org/posts/lesson-from-music/</guid>
      <description>The easiest way to live is by following trends, but the most meaningful way to live is to set new trends.
The artist who makes music to fit what is popular for audiences may find quick, short lasting fame.
Talented artists who make music that penetrates the heart, causing their audience to think about life are often not recognized by popular culture.
Most people don&amp;rsquo;t like change or thinking too deeply, but those embrace change and deep thinking will become the new ambassadors for music, because they understand and believe their message.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imitation</title>
      <link>http://rithy.org/posts/imitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 20:20:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rithy.org/posts/imitation/</guid>
      <description>Imitation is a great to train and change habit. Imitation is a way to download information from outside into our autopilot mode, if we do enough.
Base on Wikipedia, imitation is an advanced behavior whereby an individual observes and replicates anther&amp;rsquo;s behavior. Imitation is also a form of social learning that leads to the &amp;ldquo;development of traditions, and ultimately our culture.
Imitation is very powerful, so we should learn to imitate good things and habits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become Important by Thinking Your Work Is Important</title>
      <link>http://rithy.org/posts/important-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 13:45:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rithy.org/posts/important-work/</guid>
      <description>Become Important by Thinking Your Work Is Important
It&amp;rsquo;s not fair that some people are being treated more important than others. In fact, few people are treated as VIP, while many are treated like nobody. Though, life isn&amp;rsquo;t fair — throughout the history of humankind.
The reason that some people are treated as VIP is because either they think important of their work or people think they do important work, or they think their work is important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just for Today</title>
      <link>http://rithy.org/posts/just-for-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 15:46:43 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rithy.org/posts/just-for-today/</guid>
      <description>Today, I will TREAT my energy as money. I budget it, save it, find away to increase it, invest it where I would get a return.
Our energy is our true currency. Money is just a symbolic exchange of energy. This is why I must pay more attention on my energy, and invest much more wisely.
Today, I will TEAT my time as money. Because life is nothing without time, doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter how much money we have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treat as it is your LIFE</title>
      <link>http://rithy.org/posts/treat-work-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 11:25:44 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rithy.org/posts/treat-work-life/</guid>
      <description>Lets TREAT our food as our LIFE. If we low or hurt part of our LIFE, we suffer and live disease ( DIS + EASE). Not easy.
We forget that food give us our LIFE. All the food we eat should be treated as holy medicine. So when it goes into our body, it&amp;rsquo;s become our medicine to heal us and give us strange.
If there is left over that is still good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Share Fair Distibution Protocol</title>
      <link>http://rithy.org/posts/startup-share-dist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 09:42:25 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rithy.org/posts/startup-share-dist/</guid>
      <description>Some friends asked me, many time, about startup share distribution. The formula to divid share among founders and investors?
I decided to write the answer public here, so the same question will be answered in the future.
To me, there is no right way to divide share, beside keep it simple, open, and fair. Those who do more will get more. Those who do more now, get more now. If down the road of the company&amp;rsquo;s evolution, they slack-away, have the strength the share the deed with those who capable and could offer more value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A 21st Century Learning Style</title>
      <link>http://rithy.org/posts/21-century-learning-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 18:30:45 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rithy.org/posts/21-century-learning-style/</guid>
      <description>Young people today will need to succeed in a very different world than the one we’ve known – one completely outside the reach of traditional schooling.
The future is in the hands of the creative community builders, computer scientists, value creators, and entrepreneurs. The skills to identify opportunity, organize a team, plan the work, execute a task, and build reputation to successes do not come from obeying “Sit down, be quiet, and do what I say.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Need, Greed, Ambition</title>
      <link>http://rithy.org/posts/need-greed-ambition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 19:55:45 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rithy.org/posts/need-greed-ambition/</guid>
      <description>We are living in the very materialistic society order. I think it is important that we learn to split the different of words such Need, Greed, Ambition.
To me, need is a necessity. You need something to live and function. Or you need something, otherwise you can&amp;rsquo;t do the work you love.
Whereas greed is a selfish act to get what you want with the expense of others.
Ambition, on the other hand, is a desire to achieve something BIG for the benefits of many.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continue writting</title>
      <link>http://rithy.org/posts/what-is-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 20:58:53 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rithy.org/posts/what-is-it/</guid>
      <description>rithy.org is my personal space for self-expression online. A collection of record of my experiences going through life full wonder and challenges. Some of the reflection is an advice to my future Self, while some hope to be mirror for some younger people to avoid mistakes I have made over the years.
Mid-day of November 14 was when my life truely begun. The first time I truely left home to go into the world outside of my parents&#39; oversight and to pursuit something unknown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A whole universe for free</title>
      <link>http://rithy.org/posts/whole-universe-for-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 10:58:53 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rithy.org/posts/whole-universe-for-free/</guid>
      <description>I am grateful that the universe happened the way it is. I am grateful that life happen the way it is.
The univese is a great work of art, done so well by unkown force. It&amp;rsquo;s so perfect that if it made even smaller than a yocto mistake, all life as we know it would not ever existed.
Yet, we have inherit this whole universe for free. At the same time, many of us are strugling to live life, because of the society men designed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything made out of nothing</title>
      <link>http://rithy.org/posts/nothing-made-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 10:58:53 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rithy.org/posts/nothing-made-everything/</guid>
      <description>What created our universe?
Modern scientists agreed that the universe made from the big bang? Before the big bang there was nothing but a small dent point of energy which was unknown of it origin either.
Keep god and others force aside, we could conclude that universe was made out of nothing. The whole universe, everything we knew and everything that made us happy and sad &amp;ndash; and everything else was made out of nothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building From Thin Air</title>
      <link>http://rithy.org/posts/building-from-thin-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 18:35:07 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rithy.org/posts/building-from-thin-air/</guid>
      <description>Imagine making fuel, plastics, and concrete out of “thin air.&amp;quot; That’s the promise of Direct Air Capture (DAC).
Imagine making fuel, plastics, and concrete out of “thin air.&amp;quot; That’s the promise of Direct Air Capture (DAC), a technology that fundamentally disrupts our contemporary oil economy.
Mimicking what already occurs in nature, DAC essentially involves industrial photosynthesis, harnessing the power of the sun to draw carbon directly out of the atmosphere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>33 Earth Year</title>
      <link>http://rithy.org/posts/33-earth-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 12:21:57 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://rithy.org/posts/33-earth-years/</guid>
      <description>Some reflections on what I have learned and believe about life. Recently, on November 9, 2019, I celebrated 33 earth years of life on this planet.
I took a moment to reflect, and a feeling came to me that I had to ask myself as many people do, “now what?”
Just the same, I had an extraordinary feeling to be alive during this time in history to witness all the fantastic events and advancements happening around us.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
